Welcome to MyLeadX, your AI-powered CRM solution. Let's explore all the powerful features.
This is your dashboard. Get a complete overview of sales performance, leads, calls, and team activity at a glance.
The leads management page. Filter, search, and take bulk actions on all your leads from one central location.
Easily create new leads with custom fields. Capture all the information you need for effective follow-up.
Visualize your sales pipeline with our Kanban board. Drag and drop leads through different stages.
Meet our Voice AI Agents. These intelligent agents can call leads automatically in multiple languages.
Choose your agent type. Create AI voice bots, conversational agents, or IVR systems.
The Voice Agent Builder. Design your agent's conversation flow, voice, and language settings.
Our Conversational AI wizard. Create natural-sounding AI agents that can qualify leads and book meetings.
The outbound calls dashboard. Launch and monitor AI calling campaigns in real-time.
Make single calls directly from the platform. Enter a number and let AI handle the conversation.
Create calling campaigns. Upload lead lists, set schedules, and let AI agents make thousands of calls.
The Telecaller dashboard. Your human agents get scripts, click-to-call, and instant lead updates.
The call queue. Telecallers see their assigned leads and can start calling with one click.
Complete call history. Every call is recorded, transcribed, and analyzed automatically.
Live call monitoring. Listen to ongoing calls and provide real-time coaching to your team.
The analytics dashboard. Track conversion rates, revenue, call metrics, and team performance.
Advanced analytics with AI insights. Identify patterns, predict outcomes, and optimize your process.
Your conversion funnel. See exactly where leads drop off and identify optimization opportunities.
AI agent performance metrics. See how each voice agent is performing across campaigns.
Telecaller performance analytics. Track calls made, conversions, and average call duration.
The reports section. Generate detailed reports on every aspect of your sales operations.
User performance reports. See individual team member metrics and identify top performers.
AI usage reports. Track your voice minutes, AI calls, and usage across features.
AI Lead Scoring. Our AI analyzes leads and assigns priority scores based on conversion likelihood.
The customer journey view. See every interaction a lead has had with your business.
Predictive analytics. AI forecasts revenue, identifies at-risk deals, and recommends actions.
Campaign management. Create and track marketing campaigns across multiple channels.
The workflow builder. Automate repetitive tasks with visual drag-and-drop workflows.
Settings and configuration. Customize MyLeadX to match your business processes perfectly.