Welcome to MyLeadX, your AI-powered CRM solution.
The dashboard gives you a complete overview of your sales performance.
Manage all your leads with powerful filtering and bulk actions.
Visualize your sales pipeline with drag and drop stages.
Get deep insights with our analytics dashboard.
Manage user accounts and team members.
Define custom roles with specific permissions.
Meet our AI Voice Agents that call leads in 10 plus languages.
Launch outbound calling campaigns with AI agents.
Telecallers get a dedicated app for making calls.
Access complete call history with recordings and transcripts.
Create and manage marketing campaigns.
Generate detailed reports on sales operations.
Customize MyLeadX to fit your business needs.
Manage your subscription and billing.
Integrate with your tools using our API.